# Paper (Ken-Jung) Lee

paper.li@gmail.com
https://paperworkstud.io

## Brief

# UX DESIGN | PROTOTYPING | APPS | AR/VR

Paper Lee is an experienced designer with 10+ years of UI/UX design experience for mobile apps, websites, and VR/AR projects. He owns plural AR apps (Gallery AR, Fascroll, and MoCáp) in the App Store to explore the unique use cases with AR technology. He helped Diing ship its flagship VRTube in Oculus Go and multiple VR medical training programs for HTC and medical centers in Taiwan. Paper Lee devoted his early career to various mobile app and website projects. His strengths in interactive prototyping and UI/UX design motivate him to learn new stuff continuously. His proficiency in many prototyping tools, such as Xcode, Unity, Framer, Sketch, etc., ensures that he can make prototypes rapidly and frequently during the design process.

# Experience

#### PRODUCT DESIGNER

#### **VOLLEY, SAN FRANCISCO, MAR. 2022 - NOW**

UI and UX design for voice games and applications in smart speakers and smart TVs, i.e., Echo Show devices, FireTV, Roku, etc. Wireframes, voice and visual flows, prototyping, and high-fidelity visual designs.

#### LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER

#### DIING, TAIPEI / LOS ANGELES, JUN. 2016 - FEB. 2022

Define product scope, interaction, and UX landscape for mobile apps, VR/AR applications, and websites among education, entertainment, Al, and IoT. Product strategy, user research, interaction design, prototyping, visual design, UI design, technical assessment, and team leading.

#### SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

## UNIGREEN, TAIPEI, AUG. 2015 - MAY 2016

Define product scope, interaction, and UX landscape for agriculture products apps. Product strategy, principle design, user research, visual design, UI design, interaction design, prototyping, and team leading.

#### SENIOR USER INTERFACE DESIGNER

## MOBIAPPS, TAIPEI, DEC. 2012 - JUL. 2015

UI/UX design for mobile apps and websites among royalty programs, chat apps, and e-commerce. Product strategy, user research, principle design, UI design, prototyping, visual design, usability assessment, Website design & development.

# **USER INTERACTION DESIGNER**

#### PILOTFISH, MUNICH, AUG. 2011 - AUG. 2012

Design research, brainstorming, ideation, user interface design, graphic design, and prototyping.

#### **USABILITY ENGINEER**

# KATDC, TAIPEI, SEP. 2008 - JUN. 2011

In-house Usability lab build-up, prototyping, usability assessments, design system definition, and project leading for TV set-top boxes.

# MECHANICAL ENGINEER CTCI, TAIPEI, MAR. 2008 - AUG. 2008

Design the static equipment used in the chemical planet, such as pressure vessels, towers, tanks, etc. Technologic spec inspection of equipment quotation from worldwide vendors.

# Education

## M.S., BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING

#### NATIONAL YANG-MING UNIVERSITY, TAIPEI, 2005 - 2007

"3D Dynamic Model Construction for Predicting Knee Kinematics - Comparison of native knee and knee arthroplasty", presented on the 21th Congress of International Society of Biomechanics

"Three-dimensional Dynamic Model Construction for Predicting Knee Kinematics - Comparison of Native Knee and Knee Arthroplasty", Masters thesis

# B.S., MECHANICAL AND ELECTRO-MECHANICAL ENGINEERING NATIONAL SUN YAT-SEN UNIVERSITY, KAOHSIUNG, 2001 - 2005

"Man back-supporting system - A best supporting points analysis", presented on the 21th National Conference on Mechanical Engineering of CSME

## Skills

#### Tool

Sketch, Framer, Affinity Photo/Designer/Publisher, Blender, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Adobe After Effects, Lottie Animation, InVision, Marvel

HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Jekyll, React, Swift, iOS development, Android development

Unity, Xcode, Android Studio, Lens Studio, Spark AR Studio, Oculus, SteamVR, Marquette

# **User Experience Design**

Prototyping, mobile app design, web design, UI design, UX design, AR design, VR design, interaction design, visual design, User Centered Design

#### Language

Mandarine, English, German

# **Portfolio**

paperworkStudio

https://paperworkstud.io